theskinnywebsite.com 2016-06-26

# Privacy Policy — Star Style Watch

**STARSTYLEWATCH.COM** **PRIVACY POLICY**

(Updated 1/10/2016)

Thank you for visiting our site. At starstylewatch.com (“SSW”), we are committed to protecting the privacy of SSW’s online customers and visitors, and the privacy and security of any information SSW collects through the web site, www.theskinnywebsite.com (including all subpages thereto, the “Website”). SSW has prepared this Privacy Policy to highlight its commitment to your privacy and to inform you as to how SSW will use the information you entrust to SSW in connection with any products and services provided by SSW through the Website (the “Services”). If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should not access or use the Website nor should you sign up for any Services.

 **What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name and e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..

 **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

You can visit the Website on the World Wide Web without telling SSW who you are or providing SSW with any personally identifiable information. SSW collects, however, the domain names (not the email addresses unless you choose to provide your email address to SSW) of all visitors to the Website to measure the number of visits, pages visited, average time spent on the Website, etc.

SSW may also conduct online surveys to better understand the needs and profiles of visitors to the Website to measure their interest in the features of the Website. SSW does not currently collect any personal information regarding users of the site. You should note, however, that any information disclosed in public areas of the Website (such as chat rooms or comments on postings) is public information that may be viewed and collected by any party. Since we cannot control the use of information you post on public areas of the Website, you should not disclose any personally identifiable information in these public areas. For example, do not use your real name or e-mail address on any public area of the Website. If you make a posting, we suggest you use a fictitious name, or use only first name or initials. SSW reserves the right to remove any information at any time from our site that we deem inappropriate or for any other reason.

SSW may tailor its offers to you based on information you provide when you purchase products and services, from online surveys, from information that may indicate your purchasing preferences and lifestyle, as well as information available from external sources, including demographic and census data (such as ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites). With your consent, SSW may also share your email address with other reputable companies so that they can send you product and service offers that may be of interest. You will be offered an opportunity to restrict access to your email address if you object to the use of your email address by any party other than SSW. Unless it is specifically stated otherwise, when you are asked for personal information on the Website, you are agreeing to share that information with SSW.

 **How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

 **Do we use cookies?**

Yes. The Website uses a technology called “cookies” which may be used to provide you with tailored information. A cookie is a tiny element of data (a text file) that a web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive so SSW can recognize you when you return. All pages on the Website where you are prompted to log-in or that are customizable require that you accept cookies. These cookies (a) will let SSW know who you are. You may set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, however please note that by not accepting cookies from SSW, you will limit the functionality it can provide when you visit the Website.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

SSW is committed to protecting your privacy. We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Occasionally, SSW hires other companies to provide limited services on its behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, hosting websites, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. Those companies will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to deliver the service they are engaged to provide. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose.

SSW may share aggregated and anonymous demographic information with our business partners but no such information can be linked directly to any personal information about you.

Although SSW will use every reasonable effort to preserve your privacy, it may need to access and disclose certain information, including personally identifiable information, when required by federal, state local or other governmental regulations or laws. Further, SSW may access and/or disclose information we maintain about users if it believes such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on SSW; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of SSW (including the enforcement of its agreements); or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of SSW services or members of the public. In such cases, SSW will use reasonable efforts to disclose only such information as is required under the circumstances.

 **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

SSW may also allow third-party advertisement serving companies, including advertising networks, to display advertisements on the Website. Advertisement serving companies often place a persistent cookie on your computer in order to recognize your computer each time they display an online advertisement to you. Because these companies may serve advertisements on many different web sites, they may be able to compile information over time about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw and/or clicked on the advertisements they display. These companies may use this information to make predictions about your characteristics or preferences and to display targeted advertisements that they believe may be of interest to you. They may also associate this information with your subsequent visit, purchase or other activity on participating advertisers’ web sites in order to determine the effectiveness of the advertisements.

These companies may offer you a way to opt out of ad targeting based on their cookies. You may find more information by clicking on the company name on the Website and following the links to the web sites of each company.

 **Change in Ownership and Other Business Transaction**

In the event SSW goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition or the sale of all or substantially all of its assets (a “Business Transition”), information about our users will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. In such event, SSW’s custody of such information will be transferred subject to all the terms and restrictions in the then current Privacy Policy.

 **California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.

 **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

 **Amendment of Privacy Policy**

SSW will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. You can determine when the Privacy Policy was last updated by looking at the “last update” date at the top of the policy. If there are material and substantial changes to this Privacy Policy, SSW will note these changes through a prominent notice on the Website. SSW encourages you to periodically review this statement to be informed of how SSW is protecting your personal information.

 **Security**

Unfortunately no data transmission can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. While SSW strives to protect Your Information, it cannot warrant the security of the information you provide online. However, once SSW receives your information, it will do its best to ensure that its systems are functioning properly and will use reasonable and customary efforts to protect that information.

 **Notice Regarding Online Behavioral Advertising**

We allow third party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our Web site.  These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g. click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you.  These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.  To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice visit the NAI at [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).  To opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>.

 **Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Website, or your dealings with this Website, please contact [Amy](mailto:amy@starstylewatch.com) (the website owner/admin) using the contact page. Although SSW will in most circumstances be able to receive your email or other information provided through this Website, SSW does not guarantee that it will receive all such email or other information timely and accurately, or that it is legally obligated to read, act on, or respond to any such email or other information.
